byrdie.co.uk 2019-03-27

# Celebrity Beauty Secrets and Makeup Tips | Byrdie UK

Privacy Policy

Updated May 26, 2018

At Byrdie, we take online privacy seriously and we respect the concerns of our community of users. In this policy (the “Privacy Policy”) we describe our privacy practices with regard to information we collect through TheSpruce.com and its affiliated sites, TheSpruceEats.com, TheSprucePets.com, TheSpruceCrafts.com (collectively, the “Site”), to help you make informed decisions about how you share information when you visit or use the site.

Understanding How Information Is Collected on Byrdie:

Information You May Choose to Provide to Us

We may collect information, including personal data, directly from you if you choose to provide that information. For example, you may provide us with your name and contact information (such as an email address), date of birth, or other details of that nature, when you sign up for our newsletters or participate in promotions or surveys on the Site.

You also may choose to provide personally data about yourself when you participate in forums or discussions on the Site. Please be aware that information you post may be viewed or captured by anyone who visits the Site, therefore you should avoid posting sensitive or personal data that you would not want to be available to the public.

Information That Is Automatically Collected When You Visit Byrdie

When you access the Site, we and our third-party partners may automatically collect certain information about your visit using tools such as cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies. The information collected automatically when you visit the Site may include your IP address, characteristics of your operating system, information about your browser and system settings, data about the computer or mobile device you use to access the Site, unique device identifiers, clickstream data (which shows the page-by-page path you take as you browse the Site). We or our third-party partners may combine information that each of us collects automatically with other information about you, including information you choose to provide.

Cookies are small files that websites and other online services use to store information about users on the users’ own computers. This Site may use cookies (such as HTTP and HTML5 cookies and Flash cookies), as well as other types of local storage. For more information about cookies, you may visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). See the section below regarding [Your choices](https://www.thespruce.com/legal#your-choices) to learn more about how you may limit or disable cookies on your computer. If you choose to disable cookies, that could affect certain features of the Site that use cookies to enhance their functionality.

To manage our automatic data collection, we may place tags (often referred to as “web beacons”) on pages on the Site or in emails we send to you. Web beacons are small files that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies, and they may be used for a variety of purposes, such as counting the number of visitors to the Site, analyzing how users navigate around the Site, assessing how many emails that we send are actually opened and which articles or links are viewed by visitors.

We also use third-party web analytics services, such as Google Analytics, on the Site, to provide us with statistics and other information about visitors to the Site.

“Do Not Track” Signals. Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “do not track” signal to websites and online services you visit. At this time there is no consensus among industry participants as to the meaning of “do not track” in this context. Like many other websites, TheSpruce.com is not configured to respond to “do not track” signals from browsers. [Click here to learn more about "do not track" signals.](https://allaboutdnt.com/)

Finally, companies that provide certain third-party apps, tools, widgets, and plug-ins that may appear on the Site (for example, Facebook “Like” buttons), also may use automated means to collect information regarding your interactions with these features. This information collection is subject to the privacy policies or notices of those providers.

Further information regarding our use of cookies and other tracking technologies is described in our [Cookie Disclosure.](https://www.thespruce.com/legal#cookies)

How We May Use Information We Collect

We may use the information gathered on Byrdie for various purposes, including the purposes listed below. For example, if you were to contact us with a question and provide your email address, we would use the email address you provided to respond to your inquiry. In addition, we use information we collect from you and through the Site to:

  * Provide products and services you request (such as when you sign up to receive our email newsletters);
  * Respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support;
  * Offer you products and services via marketing communications, or direct you to portions of this Site or other websites, that we believe may interest you;
  * To serve advertising, content and offers to you based on your interests and online activities, from us or third parties;
  * Communicate about, and administer your participation in, events, programs, contests, and other offers or promotions;
  * Carry out, evaluate, and improve our business (which may include developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications);
  * Perform data analytics regarding usage of the Site (including market and customer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal data);
  * Guard against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements, law enforcement requests, and our company policies.

How We May Share Information

Our agents, vendors, consultants, and other service providers may have access to information we collect through the Site to carry out work on our behalf. Those parties are subject to confidentiality obligations and are restricted from using personal data collected through the Site for purposes other than to provide the requested assistance. In addition, we may share information:

  * With our affiliates for internal business purposes;
  * If we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena);
  * In response to requests from government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities;
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity;
  * With respect to analytics and statistical information, to inform advertisers about the nature of our user base;
  * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation); and
  * With your consent or at your discretion.

Your Choices

Unsubscribe from emails. To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of that email newsletter. If you would like to globally opt-out from ALL Byrdie email campaigns, please send an email to [optout@TheSpruce.com](mailto:optout@thespruce.com) with "Unsubscribe" in the subject line. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honor your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.

Blocking cookies. Certain browsers may be configured to notify you when you receive cookies, or allow you to restrict or disable certain cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, that could affect certain features of the Site that use cookies to enhance their functionality.

Disabling local shared objects (“Flash cookies”). We may use other kinds of local storage that function similarly, but are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies. Your browser may allow you to disable its HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in its HTML5 local storage. [Click here](http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html) for details about deleting information contained in "local shared objects" or adjusting related preferences.

Options concerning third-party ad networks. For more information about third-party ad networks and services that use these technologies, you can visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and [click here](http://aboutads.info/choices) to opt out or to learn more about your options. You also may visit the [NAI's site for additional options ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices)on how to opt out of interest-based advertising.

How We Protect Personal Data.

We maintain appropriate administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal data you provide against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure, or use. That said, it is not possible to guarantee the security of information transmitted online, and you assume some risk with regard to the security of information you provide through any website, including this Site. If you have a data security inquiry, you may contact us by emailing [security@thespruce.com](mailto:security@thespruce.com). To request an invite to our bug bounty program to submit reports on vulnerabilities found on TheSpruce.com, you may contact us by emailing [bugbounty@thespruce.com](mailto:bugbounty@thespruce.com).

Links From Byrdie to Other Websites

On this Site, we may provide links to other websites that are controlled by third parties. Linked websites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. We are not responsible for the content, usage terms, privacy policies, or any other aspects of websites that we do not own or control.

Surveys and Quizzes

While you are visiting Byrdie, you may have the opportunity to participate in surveys, quizzes, or other interactive features that request information about you and your opinions and preferences. Your participation in these features is entirely voluntary. If you do choose to participate, please be aware that these features may be operated by a third party that is not controlled by Byrdie, and therefore the information you provide may be collected by the third party and subject to its privacy policy.

Children’s Privacy

This Site is not designed or intended for use by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 16. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from a child under the age of 16, we will delete any such information.

Information for Users Outside the United States

Your personal data may be stored, transferred and process in and to the United States and in other countries by our affiliates and/or service providers. The data protection laws in these countries may provide a lower standard of protection for your personal data than your country of residence. We take great care in protecting your personal data and have put in place adequate mechanisms to protect it when it is transferred internationally. We will transfer your personal data in compliance with applicable data protection laws and will implement suitable safeguards to ensure that your personal data is adequately secured by any third party that will access your information (for instance, by using the Model Clauses as approved by the European Commission).

By using our Site and providing personal data to us, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the collection, use, maintenance, transfer to and processing of your personal data in the United States or other countries or territories, and, unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we use this consent as the legal basis for that data transfer.

If you have questions or wish to obtain more information about the international transfer of your personal data or the implemented safeguards, please send us an email to [privacy@byrdie.com](mailto:privacy@byrdie.com)

How We’ll Inform You About Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this online privacy policy periodically to reflect changes to our privacy practices, such as how we collect or use personal data. We will post a prominent notice on the TheSpruce.com home page to notify you of significant changes to this policy, and we indicate at the top of the policy the date when it was most recently updated.

How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy or about our privacy practices, you may contact us by emailing [privacy@byrdie.com](mailto:privacy@byrdie.com).

If you are a California resident inquiring about your California privacy rights, please include “California privacy rights request” in the subject line of your email. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area inquiring about your rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), please include “GDPR privacy rights request” in the subject line of your email.

You may also write to:

Byrdie Privacy   
1500 Broadway, 6th Floor   
New York, NY 10036

JURISDICTION SPECIFIC PROVISIONS  
Our Notice to California Residents

Subject to certain limits, under California law California residents may ask us to provide them with a list of the categories of personal data that we have disclosed to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, as well as the identity of those third parties. California residents may contact us as specified in the [How to Contact Us section](https://www.thespruce.com/legal#contact) above to make a request for this information.

If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA):

  1. Controller of your Personal Data

The controller of your personal data under this Privacy Policy is About, Inc., with an address of 1500 Broadway, 6th Floor, New York, NY 10036. Our local representative with respect to the GDPR can be contacted at [Privacy@ask.co.uk](mailto:Privacy@ask.co.uk).

  2. Legal Bases for Using Personal Data

We process your personal data only if we have a legal basis to do so, including:

  1. to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations;
  2. for the performance of our contract with you or to take steps at your request before entering into a contract;
  3. for our legitimate interests or those of a third party;
  4. where you have given consent to our specific use.

The purpose for which we use and process your information and the legal basis on which we carry out each type of processing is further explained below.

Purposes for which we will process the information

| 

Legal Basis for the processing  
  
---|---  
  
To provide products and services you request.

| 

It is necessary for us to process your personal data in order to deliver the services and process transactions according to the applicable contract between us.  
  
To respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support.

| 

It is necessary for us to respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support in order to take steps at your request or according to the applicable contract between us.  
  
To offer you products and services in marketing communications, or direct you to portions of this Site or other websites, that we believe may interest you.

| 

We may send electronic marketing communications to you if you have consented to these communications. It is in our legitimate interest to market out products and services to you by other means and to direct you to portions of this Site or other websites that we believe may interest you. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
  
To communicate about, and administer your participation in, events, programs, contests, and other offers or promotions

| 

We will send electronic communications to you if you have consented to these communications. With respect to other communications, it is in our legitimate interest to communicate to you and administer your participation in, our events, programs, contests, and other offers or promotions. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
  
To carry out, evaluate, and improve our business (which may include developing new features for the Site; analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the Site; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications.

| 

It is in our legitimate interests to process your personal data to carry out these activities. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
  
To perform data analytics regarding usage of the Site (including market and customer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal data).

| 

It is in our legitimate interests to process your personal data to carry out these activities. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
  
To serve advertising, content and offers to you based on your interests and online activities, from us or third parties.

| 

We will serve you advertising, content and offers to you based on your interests and online activities if you have consented to this processing.  
  
To enable our affiliates or service providers to perform certain activities on our behalf;

| 

It is necessary for us to process your personal data in this manner in order to deliver the services and process transactions according to the applicable contract between us. It is also in our legitimate interest to enable our service providers and affiliates to perform certain activities on our behalf. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
  
To notify you of any changes to the Website that may affect you.

| 

It is necessary for us to process your personal data in order to deliver the services and process transactions according to the applicable contract between us.  
  
  * If we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena);
  * In response to requests from government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities;
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity; and
  * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation)

| 

We conduct this processing to comply with our legal obligations and to protect the public interest.  
  
  * Guard against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements, law enforcement requests, and our company policies.

| 

We conduct this processing to comply with our legal obligations and to protect the public interest.  
  
  1. International Transfers

Some of our processing of your data will involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). Some of our external third-party service providers are also based outside of the EEA, and their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. This includes the United States. Where personal data is transferred to and stored in a country not determined by the European Commission as providing adequate levels of protection for personal data, we take steps to provide appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data, including when appropriate entering into standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, obliging recipients to protect your personal data.

  2. Retention of Personal Data

We will retain your personal data only for as long as necessary for the purposes it was retained, such as to enable you to use the Website and your products or to provide services to you. In some instances, we may retain data for longer periods in order to comply with applicable laws (including those regarding document retention), resolve disputes with any parties, and otherwise as necessary to allow us to conduct our business. All personal data we retain will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our internal retention guidelines.

  3. Data Subject Access Rights

You have the following rights:

  * Right of access to your personal data: You have the right to ask us for confirmation on whether we are processing your personal data, and access to the personal data and related information.
  * Right to correction: You have the right to have your personal data corrected, as permitted by law.
  * Right to erasure: You have the right to ask us to delete your personal data, as permitted by law.
  * Right to withdraw consent: You have the right to withdraw consent that you have provided.
  * Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority: You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in the member state of your habitual residence.
  * Right to restriction of processing: You have the right to request the limiting of our processing under limited circumstances.
  * Right to data portability: You have the right to receive the personal data that you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and you have the right to transmit that information to another controller, including to have it transmitted directly, where technically feasible.
  * Right to object: You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, as permitted by law, under limited circumstances.

In order to exercise any of these rights, please contact us according to the [“How to Contact Us” section](https://www.thespruce.com/legal#contact) herein. Please note that the above rights are not absolute and we may be entitled to refuse requests, wholly or partly, where exceptions under the applicable law apply.

Byrdie Cookie Disclosure

**Provider** |  **Name of cookie** |  **Purpose** |  **Type** |  **Duration**  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
Provider

| 

Name of cookie

| 

Purpose

| 

Type

| 

Duration  
  
Google Analytics

| 

_ga

| 

Used to distinguish users.

| 

Persistent

| 

2 Years  
  
Google Analytics

| 

_gid

| 

Used to distinguish users.

| 

Persistent

| 

24 Hours  
  
Google Analytics

| 

_gat_<property-id>

| 

Used to throttle request rate.

| 

Persistent

| 

1 Minute  
  
Dotdash

| 

TMog

| 

Dotdash client id - Used to identify unique browsers

| 

Persistent

| 

68 Years  
  
Dotdash

| 

Mint

| 

Dotdash session id - Used to identify all activity within a session

| 

Persistent

| 

30 Minutes  
  
Dotdash

| 

pc

| 

pagecount

| 

Persistent

| 

30 Minutes  
  
Dotdash

| 

ds_ab

| 

AB Testing segmentation information

| 

Session  
  
Google (GTM/GA)

| 

_dc_gtm_<property-id>

| 

Used to throttle request rate.

| 

Persistent

| 

1 Minute  
  
SailThru

| 

sailthru_pageviews

| 

Page view count by user on site

| 

Persistent

| 

30 Minutes  
  
SailThru

| 

sailthru_content

| 

Tracks recent pageviews for visitor

| 

Persistent

| 

1 Hour  
  
SailThru

| 

sailthru_visitor

| 

Client Id

| 

Persistent

| 

1 Hour  
  
Google DFP

| 

__gads

| 

Ad targeting

| 

Persistent

| 

2 Years  
  
Google

| 

gsScrollPos-<num>

| 

Scroll position tracking

| 

Session  
  
Bounce Exchange

| 

bounceClientVisit<num>v

| 

Client tracking information

| 

Persistent

| 

30 Minutes  
  
Google

| 

AMP_TOKEN

| 

Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service.

| 

Persistent

| 

1 Hour  
  
Quantcast

| 

__qca

| 

Collects anonymous data on the user's visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded with the purpose of generating reports for optimising the website content.

| 

Persistent

| 

13 Months  
  
Advertising Policy

To help us maintain the resources needed to create the quality content you deserve, we accept advertisements on our Site. We greatly value transparency and hope that this policy leaves you feeling even more confident about the content and service we provide.

Byrdie maintains a distinct separation between advertising and editorial content.

  * All advertising or sponsored content on Byrdie is clearly and unambiguously distinguished from editorial content through borders or other distinguishing elements and/or identified as an "Ad," "Advertisement," "Sponsored" or a similar designation indicating that the content is being provided by or on behalf of an advertiser or sponsor.
  * All "native" ads or paid content are identified as an "Ad," "Advertisement," "Sponsored" or a similar designation indicating that the content is being provided by or on behalf of an advertiser or sponsor.
  * Editorial content on Byrdie is not influenced by advertisements unless the content is sponsored content, in which case, the content will be clearly demarcated and/or identified with the title "Ad," "Advertisement," or "Sponsored", or a similar designation, indicating that the content is being provided by or on behalf of an advertiser or sponsor.
  * All advertisements and sponsored content appearing on Byrdie are subject to the Guidelines found [here ](https://www.thespruce.com/legal#advertising-guidelines).

Ecommerce and Affiliate Links Disclosure.

Contributors and/or Byrdie may receive compensation for participation in third-party affiliate marketing programs, including purchases made through links to Byrdie’s e-commerce partners, if any. Pages on the Site containing affiliate marketing links, including product reviews, will be demarcated and/or identified with a disclaimer.

Advertising Guidelines

These advertising guidelines (“Guidelines”) set forth standards that govern the placement and display of advertisements and sponsored content (collectively, “Ads”) by any advertiser, agency, or advertising technology platform (collectively, “Advertisers”). Advertisers must adhere to these Guidelines when placing Ads, including Ads purchased under the AAAA/IAB Standard Terms and Conditions, on websites or mobile properties owned or controlled by About, Inc., including Byrdie.com (collectively, “Byrdie”).

These Guidelines are intended to provide general parameters for Advertisers in connection with Ad creative and content served on Byrdie. They are not exhaustive and do not address every situation or issue that may arise in the course of business. Accordingly, these Guidelines are subject to change from time to time in Byrdie’s sole and absolute discretion.

Advertisers are responsible for understanding and complying with all applicable laws and regulations, including FTC guidelines regarding advertising, native advertising disclosures, endorsements, privacy, and data security. All Ad’s must be fair, truthful, and clearly distinguishable from editorial content. Advertisers are responsible for ensuring all Ads and related claims are adequately substantiated. Further, Advertisers must adhere to Byrdie’s Prohibited Content Guidelines and Additional Standards set forth below, which are incorporated into and made a part of these Guidelines.

Ads served through networks or exchanges are reviewed on a regular basis and, in addition to any other remedies Byrdie may have, Byrdie reserves the right to remove, without notice, any Ads that do not meet these Guidelines, regardless of whether the Ad was previously accepted by Byrdie.

PROHIBITED CONTENT

Ads may not contain or promote the following:

  * Drugs/Alcohol/Tobacco. Ads may not promote illegal drugs, illegal substances, abuse of prescription drugs, use of Alcohol (except for beer and wine), or tobacco products, or any related paraphernalia thereto. Lawful products and services which promote quitting tobacco related products are permitted.
  * Weapons/Violence. Ads may not promote the use, distribution, or making of firearms, ammunition, explosives, pyrotechnics or other weapons. Ads may not promote violence, cruelty, or physical or emotional harm to any person or animal.
  * Illegal Activities/Gambling. Ads may not promote any illegal or other questionable activities which may be illegal in one or more jurisdictions, including without limitation hacking, counterfeiting, or other activities that may violate the intellectual property, privacy, publicity, or contractual rights of others. Ads may not contain or promote content related to scams, financial schemes, pyramid schemes or other fraudulent or illegal financial or investment opportunities. Ads may not promote casinos, gambling, betting, numbers games, sports or financial betting. Ads promoting state lotteries arepermitted.
  * Hate/Intolerance/Discrimination. Ads may not contain or promote hate speech, personal attacks, or discrimination toward any individual, group, country or organization.
  * Obscenity/Indecency/Profanity. Ads may not contain or promote any obscene, indecent, profane or offensive words, images, sounds, videos or other content.
  * Political/Religious. Ads may not contain hostile, offensive, inflammatory or hateful speech related to political or religious topics or groups. Ads may not exploit controversial political, social, or religious issues for commercial purposes.
  * Sexual/Adult Content. Ads may not include full or partial nudity, depictions of people in explicit positions, or activities that are overly suggestive or sexually provocative. Ads will not contain text or images exposing anyone or anything involved in explicit sexual acts or lewd and lascivious behavior. Ads may not promote escort, dating, erotic massage, pornography, or other sexual products or services.
  * Disparagement/Defamation. Ads may not contain disparaging or defamatory information or content which tends to harm the reputation of Byrdie or any other individual, group, or organization.
  * Gross Depictions. Ads may not contain or promote content that is crude, vulgar, degrading or likely to shock or disgust.
  * Militant/Extremism. Ads may not contain or promote extremely aggressive and combative behaviors or unlawful political measures, including individuals or groups advocating violence as a means to achieve their goals.
  * Sensitive Content. Ads may not target sensitive categories such as financial status, medical conditions, mental health, criminal record, political affiliation, age, racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical affiliation or beliefs, sexual behavior or orientation, or trade union membership.
  * Free Goods/Services. Ads may not distribute or promise to distribute any free goods and services.
  * Targeted at Children. Ads may not specifically target children, including through cartoons or other similar content.
  * Unverifiable Claims. Ad’s may not make confusing claims that reasonable consumers cannot readily understand and evaluate.
  * Before/After Images. Ad may not depict “before and after” images or images that contain unexpected or unlikely results.
  * Health/Safety Claims. Ads may not promote actions likely to harm one’s health, such as bulimia, anorexia, binge drinking, or drug use. Ads may not make health claims that are not clearly substantiated. Advertisers may be required to submit supporting documentation to substantiate their products’ claims.
  * Misleading/False/Deceptive: Ads may not contain any information or content that is potentially misleading, false, or deceptive, including content which is meant to deceptively generate clicks such as fake “close” buttons.
  * Competitive to Byrdie /Affiliates. Ads may not promote direct competitors of Byrdie or any of its parent, affiliate, subsidiary or other related entity.

ADDITIONAL STANDARDS

Advertisers and Ads must adhere to the following:

  * Audio/Animation. Ads may not include overly disruptive audio or animation that plays automatically.
  * Popups/Downloads. Ads may not include lead ads, floating layers, pop-ups, surveys, or any digital downloads.
  * Malicious Software. Ads may not contain malicious code, software or viruses, including malware, spyware, adware, stealware, or Trojan horses.
  * Separation. Ads must contain clear boarders and be displayed so they are unmistakably not part of Byrdie’s editorial site content.
  * Phishing. Ads may not trap or trick a user into providing money or any account, personal or other sensitive information.
  * Compatibility. Ads must function uniformly on both Apple and PC formats, as well as all major Internet browsers.
  * Independence. Ads may not appear to compromise or influence Byrdie’s editorial independence from Advertisers.
  * Endorsements. Ads may not create or imply the existence of any endorsement by Byrdie of any product, service or organization.
  * Landing Pages. Landing pages associated with Ads must correspond to the Ad's "call to action" and not engage in “bait and switch”.
  * Proprietary Rights. Ads may not violate any copyright, trademark, trade-secret, patent, publicity, privacy, or other proprietary rights of Byrdie or any third party. Advertisers may not alter or interfere with the readability or display of any Byrdie trademarks, service marks, logos, designs or slogans.
  * Data Collection/Use. Ads may not include open-box forms to register users or collect any data. Ads may not collect and sell or license any data or mailing lists regarding Byrdie users without Byrdie's express permission. Advertisers may not collect any personally identifiable information from Byrdie users or place any cookies, applets or other similar files, if those files transmit any personally identifiable information to Advertisers, on desktop computers or mobile devices of Byrdie users. Advertisers must handle data with appropriate care, not misuse any data which they are permitted to collect, nor collect any data for unclear purposes or without appropriate security measures.
